A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars, SG 3, Series 13 FA1474
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars, SG 3, Series 13
1992-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1474
6.65 Cubic Feet 17 letter-size document boxes, and 1 half-document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC in 2002 as accession 2002:066.
Scope and Contents
This series contains program files, planning, and meeting records of the Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars Program. The majority of the material is grant administration files documenting the planning and implementation of the Picker Scholars Program. These records often include: proposals, administration and budget files, grant products, evaluation reports, related correspondence and background material. The series also contains files for each of the Picker Scholars 1993-1996. The scholars files include interim and final reports, administration of the fellowship, and related correspondence.
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Lisa Cooper Patrick (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - J. Randall Curtis (96045) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Finalists (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted - Confidential material
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Osborn - Picker 1996-1997 Program Direction (96949) - Administration, Budget, Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Osborn - Picker 1996-1997 Program Direction (96949) - Proposal Development (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Osborn - Picker 1996-1997 Program Direction (96949) - Grant Products (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1996 Picker Scholars - Terri Fried (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1996 Picker Scholars - Jody Heymann, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1996 Picker Scholars - Robert Kitzmann, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1996 Picker Scholars - Jaya K. Rao, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1996 Picker Scholars - Michael Rodriquez, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 1996 Pickers Scholars - Finalists (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Picker-Commonwealth Fund Annual Meeting, 1998 June 23-24 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Picker - Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR), 1995 July (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (95-12) - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2-4)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (95-12) - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars Program (94-19) - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars Program (94-19) - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Picker-Commonwealth Fund Advisory Meeting, 1995 April (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (95-12) - Administration and Budget (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (95-12) - Grant Products (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (95-12) - Proposal Development, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (96002) - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (96002) - Administration (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (96002) - Grant Products (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Osborn - Administration of Picker Scholars (96002) - Deliverables (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Picker-Commonwealth Fund Scholars Program Annual Meeting, 1996 June 7-8 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Finalists (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Christine Laine, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Susan Dorr Goold, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
- 1995 Picker Scholars - Ira Wilson, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Krimgold - Picker Scholars 1997-1998 Support for Program Direction (970941) - Grant Products (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Krimgold - Picker Scholars 1997-1998 Support for Program Direction (970941) - Proposal Development (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - Krimgold - Picker Scholars 1997-1998 Support for Program Direction (970941) - Administration and Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Association for Health Services Research (AHSR) - (990043) - 1999 Meeting Grant, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Picker Scholars Next Generation (92-44), 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Picker Scholars Next Generation (92-44), 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- AHSR - FHSR Conference, 1995 June (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Picker Scholars Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Picker Scholars Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Finalists (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Selections (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - John Hornberger, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Richard Kravitz, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Robert F. Nease, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Annie Steinberg, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Gary Rosenthal, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Administration of Picker Scholars Program (94-19) - Administration and Budget, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Administration of Picker Scholars Program (94-19) - Grant Products, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Finalists (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Osborn - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Robert Fullilove, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Edward Guadagnoli, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Edward Guadagnoli, 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Lisa Harris, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Sarah Shannon, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - David H. Thom, 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 1993 Picker Scholars - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- 1994 Picker Scholars - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2-4)
- Foundation for Health Services Research (FHSR) - Administration of Picker Scholars Program (94-19) - Articles and Background Information, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Picker/Commonwealth Fund - Ambulatory Care Meetings, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Management Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2-5)
- Possible Commonwealth Fund Medicare Program, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Quality of Life at the End of Life Survey Topics, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Picker Business Plan, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Executive Nurse Fellowship Program Retreat, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Advisory Committee - Jewish Hospital - Restraint Minimization, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Advisory Committee - Restraint Minimization, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars Program - Annual Meeting 1995, 1995 June 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Thomas Delbanco, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars Brochure (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 April 14 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Picker/Commonwealth Fund Scholars Advisory Committee Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1993 March 16 (Box 18, Folder 4)